<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Weather</string>
    <string name="input_location_name">Введите местоположение</string>
    <string name="Minimal">Мин.</string>
    <string name="Maximal">Макс.</string>
    <string name="not_added_list_cities">Не удалось получить список городов</string>
    <string name="not_added_city">Не удалось добавить город</string>
    <string name="not_delete_city">Не удалось удалить город</string>
    <string name="not_load_hourly_weather">"Не удалось загрузить погоду за день в "</string>
    <string name="not_load_daily_weather">"Не удалось загрузить погоду за неделю в "</string>
    <string name="not_searched_city">Не удалось найти город</string>
    <string name="now">Сейчас</string>
    <string name="today">Сегодня</string>
    <string name="location_access_rationale_details_text">\t\tYour permission is required to accurately determine your location. Without this permission, the location may be inaccurate and the weather information incorrect.
        \n\t\tPlease confirm your consent to access your location by clicking on the button below.
    </string>
    <string name="location_permission_rationale">The fine location permission is needed for core functionality.</string>

    <string name="background_location_permission_rationale">The background location permission is needed for enhanced functionality.</string>
    <string name="background_location_access_rationale_details_text">\t\tTo have your location automatically updated when you\'re not using the app, you need tap \"Allow all the time\".
        \n\t\tThus, by launching the application, you will immediately receive the correct weather information for your location. So you will speed up the time to receive accurate weather information for your location.
        \n\t\tPlease confirm your consent to update your location all the time by clicking on the button below.</string>
    <string name="all_permission_rationale">The fine location permission is needed for core functionality. The background location permission is needed for enhanced functionality.</string>
    <string name="all_location_permission_rationale_details">\t\tYour permission is required to accurately determine your location. Without this permissions, the location may be inaccurate and the weather information incorrect.
        \n\t\tAlso, in order for your location data to be automatically updated when you are not using the application, you must click \"Allow all the time\".
        \n\t\tThus, by launching the application next time, you will immediately receive the correct weather information for your location.
        \n\t\tPlease confirm your consent to access your location and using all the time by clicking on the button below.</string>
    <string name="enable_fine_location_button_text">Approve Location Access</string>
    <string name="enable_background_location_button_text">Approve update location all the time</string>
    <string name="enable_all_permission_button_text">Approve permissions</string>

    <string name="ok">OK</string>
</resources>